NELSON **DALY**

nelson.daly@outlook.com | nelsond.tech

About Me

An inquisitive and proactive Front-End Developer, with strong problem-solving skills and experience delivering results in a fast-paced environment. Able to communicate effectively with all levels of seniority and degrees of technical understanding. Experienced in project leadership and stakeholder management.

Skills

TypeScript / JavaScript | Angular 13+ | HTML5 | CSS3 | RxJS | NgRx | Karma | Jasmine | Java 8

Demonstrable Experience

Portfolio Web App (nelsond.tech/this.app)

• Developed a Single-Page Application in the style of a code editor, using Angular 13 and TypeScript, featuring a resizable preview section showcasing live demonstrations of the following additional projects built.

Issue Tracker App (nelsond.tech/issuetracker.app)

• Designed and developed a CRUD web application, featuring vanilla JavaScript chart visualizations.

Scientific Calculator App (nelsond.tech/scicalculator.app)

• Created an emulation of Casio fx-991MS. Implemented 80% functionality for the minimum viable product.

Local Weather Forecast App (nelsond.tech/localweather.app)

• Built a live weather forecast widget, consuming JSON data from a third-party REST API / microservice.

Career History

Enprod

Technical Consultant

2021 – Present

• Providing varying technical consulting, presently focused on front-end web development using Angular.

Goldman Sachs

Support – Engineering Division

2013 - 2021

• Provided support to cross-region Engineering teams, across multiple Business Units, for numerous management systems, processes and projects. Developed Confluence, SharePoint and internal websites. Analyzed data and distributed weekly reports.

Education

University of Pennsylvania

2020 - 2021

- <u>Professional Certificate</u> in Computer Science Essentials for Software Development
 - Certificate for SD1x: Software Development Fundamentals
 - Certificate for SD2x: Data Structures and Software Design
 - Certificate for SD3x: Algorithm Design and Analysis
 - Certificate for SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript

Microsoft 2020

- Certificate for DEV262x: Logic and Computational Thinking
- Certificate for DAT201x: Querying Data with T-SQL
- Certificate for DAT206x: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Excel

British Academy of New Music

2011 - 2013

• Level 3 RSL Extended Diploma for Music Technology